Hmm
Hi
I think that is
Yeah, be careful Ben because I was you could tell I don't he sound like I already know what he sound like already
That's how I need that's that gets it
Yeah, my mic sound crispy, but yeah, man, we already know who the fuck it is man
It sounds just like how it's weird that there's people in life that gets some type of
High feeling by going on panels and saying that word. You get what I'm saying? You got a
Don't kick them off block that because they're gonna have to make hundreds of art emails to keep coming up here
I don't think you block them. I don't think you've been that email
You got a band that email that way they don't come back up here. You know
And then again, Kate's gonna say some shit in chat. I'm not trying to do nothing
All I had was a discussion about what she was talking about earlier in regards to Sammy peps 2.0
Now she over here crying talking about I'm doing something to put your channel jeopardize like or in jeopardy man
Get out of here, bro. Damn. I can't talk about shit without her stupid ass coming over here
Yeah, oh, okay, oh here's easy
We're blind to you haters the fuck is wrong with you fat fucking bitch
We're talking she said oh, I think hey, she said Tony over. I want that page and she was like I love you Tony. Thank you, daddy. Oh
That was her. She said that on her show
Yes, you I love
That bitch is so like, come on, bro.
Like, I ain't got nothing to say.
Like, if you was a petty motherfucker right now,
if you was a petty motherfucker,
you would end your stream and strike that bitch
and take her handle down, leave her out for a couple days.
Ha ha, learn your lesson, bitch.
Yeah
First strike anybody that gets Kate a strike. I will cash out you a hundred
replaying a hundred
Not you don't got nothing. What'd you talk about psych? I'm talking about any but she plays every a lot of people shit
If you if somebody's able to get that bitch I got a hundo for you
spotted by
It don't even have to be a person
A hundo get that bitch a strike for for fucking restreaming people without their permission
I was saying, I didn't want to come back, I was enjoying the show and that's why I came up with it because I got pissed to fuck off and this bad thing did that shit, bro.
But you know what, Elda, you know what, Elda, like, um, you know how she, she like screamed about how someone used her picture, like...
on uh, either in the chat or as an avatar on the on the
Streamyard, they can't use them at all. You can't use it in her picture, but then she
She lets Tony
Use my pick my
To him doesn't say shit to him nothing. Oh
That's what we're using it and then I told you okay. Yeah
And uh, that's that asshole. Oh, yeah, okay
Yeah, there's like this really just like
Just think there's just trash to be over this place. They're like saying the worst thing. There's like basically like
Like, you know cancel me or whatever like so much people are saying it so I'm still here, so
They look you a console, that's it
That's to be honest
Well, I know I'm gonna sit back and watch again. I'm gonna sit back and watch and if anything else I'll come up
It's hopefully later, bro. Okay
Mmm
I've been taught to I mean, I haven't talked to Kate really in a little like a little while. Well, I didn't
But money all you got to do is get her one good time and you get a
Yeah, although we did the other thing out of it cuz they all it'll just make her
There's not
You know, I don't want her to lay. I don't want to create a strike war or anything
So it's like I'm just gonna say I don't endorse any anybody doing strike
That's a W between El Doe and anybody else. I didn't do that. Don't raise you here
You ain't got to but it's people out there that can do it. So again, if you can strike the bitch
I got a hundo for you
easy
Well, yeah
All I need is a cash app and proof that she got strike
You know, no, I can't got nothing to do with this. I'm just letting people know man. So you ain't got a site game with all that
He not doing it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and I really
Want to make things worse so
Yeah, but I never said anything to Kate. I've been on the show a few times. She's let me explain myself
We talked for Julie and everything and uh, so I
Manipulate she's just like beat us she tries to tell you what the fuck to do
Tries to tell you how to run your channel. Oh, thank you better. You know man
He gonna ruin you like what the fuck I'm saying is can do nothing to site channel nothing like
because it's you you got a problem with it like get the fuck out of here you
allow fucking allied to use this fucking patron don't say a fucking thing
fucking mentally to say i'm just gonna let him know you're mentally disabled and you need to
get the fuck off the internet that's all you feel me right you threaten beta not that i give a
fuck about beta anymore but you go with the beta right so why you gotta promise it's done to you
hoe
Hi fuck out of here
Hey, what's up, yo?
What up, though?
How are you?
Dingle. Hey, jingle. How are you?
Hmm. Yeah, I'm gonna try to do it. I've been drawing pictures of uh, okay. Oh, I think this is KK. Hold on
Hold on hold on site good confirm with her enough in the chat, please
I don't think it is because it's like some ridiculous other names. So I'm gonna leave that for that's not KK
That's not KK. Bam. They almost had you see KK is you backstage KK?
And someone and someone if they type in the chat someone have to verify
They should have to verify in the fucking chat they should have to verify
No, it's no
That's like that. That's not cake. It. Oh
It's a
Chat it's some strange photo. Oh, she said it's her. Oh, oh, it's her. Okay. Oh, yeah
Like she like weeners
Hey kicking your member of my your member of my yeah, see that's how I your member verified. That's awesome
Did she pay for that's the question
Who cares although
I'm saying I'm probably paid for half the motherfucking people on your just say it man
What's up KK what the problem is man? I see over there kissing Kate ass. What's going on with that man?
I am not kissing anybody's ass. I was coming to make sure you were good
So you know what's going on? No, how are you making sure I'm good if you was up there way before I was?
What?
I'm talking about you was up there kissing Kate. You was up on Kate platform. Now you now you buddy buddy
So what I was well, I don't have no issues with her. Oh my god
I don't I don't really have like issues with anybody necessarily. I'm I'm a little bit like happy
So I don't give a fuck
Like I don't care. I'll do how who hasn't snaked me
In the time I've been alone like who hasn't thanked you. I'll know you know what I'm saying
I don't care anymore. You don't even come around like so many boring characters. They're just fucking boring
They're all boring. Boring as fuck.
Like who the fuck is, uh, juice the show?
Who's a juice other than some fucking creepy predator
that fucking admits to fucking recording women in the shower
without their knowledge?
He did it. He did it.
Yo, he screamers shot at that young girl's boobs.
Yeah
That girl boob and made it his profile picture man. Yeah, come on. Yep. Yep bloggers
Yeah, cuz he wanted to show her that she was porn bombing herself get the fuck out of here
I think it's a fucking weirdo, man
You're weirdo, man. Damn. So I thought he was recording you so you didn't know he was recording. Oh, of course not
But Eldo, did you hear that the actual screenshot that he posted where he blacked out everything?
I was actually dressed in but he was saying I was in the shower
but I was wearing pants in the screenshot that he tried to
Black out the whole top of it to say that that was me in the shower. I was showing him
My tattoos I assume
I don't give a fuck what the guy says. I didn't fucking do that which makes it even weirder
So you was a native at all. I mean, there was no
Was that with a khaki khaki pants
Or do they blend into your skin like I don't know I'm sorry. There's a red joke
Hello
She probably doing something but yeah, that shit weird though
That shit weird for him to try to he probably forgot you know I'm saying but for him to even point blank period for him to just be
Scream recording the shit
You know I'm saying is it's just where you you got to think of that mindset like
Like are you jerking off the fucking KK fucking skin her tattoo?
No, he showed a thing that that that call was allegedly an hour and 42 minutes that he scream record that whole fucking call
That's weird. He's known. He says he scream records people's lives
Can you imagine him sitting there while he on the phone with people and just scream record in the fucking whole?
Conversation, I think he'll wear it over here. We're gonna
That was weird
Like and listen, I'm not even kidding that shit with the breakfast every time I fucking hear him talking
He's talking something about his breakfast. All right. It's the same fucking thing
That's what people have to talk about since you know like people like, you know
Maybe you or myself aren't around as much because it's so boring
So that's what he talks about his breakfast. Yeah, the motherfucker says he goes jogging every morning at 530 in the morning
Have you seen him? He's built like a goddamn tank. Tell me where he's fucking jogged
That fat motherfucker does not dog. He'll only do a smoke weed and eat
Come on, man. It's so fat
You know what, before he quit his job and got that inheritance, do you know that he used to call out of work, at least, I would say the average would be once a week.
Like average is once a week.
That's a black thing. Oh wait, that's racist.
I'm just saying my girlfriend be love me. I'm saying like yeah, I mean I've been lazy too
Also, he got an inheritance as it went because his mom died or somebody else died he'll yeah, he lost both his
He finally got that money, huh? That's why he wanted to take me to France chill
Hello, I'm shoes. So choose the one of the many ETC sims wants to show you something
What there's so many names use
Let me show you show me what you got show me like what are you talking about?
What you got to show me?
Damn, okay, so he got inheritance. That's why he put his die. I was wondering like why does one fuck of this
You know, he said he just, you know, went ahead and quit. Oh, he got some money money.
Yo, he quit his job of 10 years and started sending me stupid money out of nowhere. All right.
From one day to the next. He was sending me 50, 100 in the same day. In the same day, I would go live and he would hit me back to back like.
and it was after he quit because he got that inheritance and he thinks he's important now
because he's got new money but he's gonna learn he's gonna learn you know that
don't let that baby mama find out nigga she's gonna take all your shit that's fake baby mama he
doesn't have no damn kid you think anybody would let juice impregnate them do you think anybody
Nah, not really. I mean, shit. Dang, he ain't got no baby mind. That was a lie. Come on,
man. And he ain't heard giving. Y'all ladies, y'all hear that? He got an inheritance. I
better get him because he gonna be giving that money out like it's nothing.
i'm telling you right now if anybody has the patience for him they listen not me they could call me
whatever the fuck they want i don't give a fuck how much money a man has if i don't like you i don't
like you and fucking juice is the pure fucking example right goddamn there that man was throwing
at least a couple hundred dollars at me a week and i told him to go fuck himself
then that's wild man damn you hear that hammer she was getting that money money
money nice you've been talking about me oh yeah listen mm-hmm they've they've been
fucking the whole time can't nobody tell me they are really they are really moving with
Oh my god, this nigga. Oh my god. He down bad if he really moved in with jade
Cuz that's where peps is that right with that girl jade?
That nigga fell off man. God damn. He fell off boy. He had to move in with his fucking with with with pebs
Can you imagine falling off that bad though, Eldo?
Who would have thought this is like the kingpin, you know, he's gonna take everybody down
You're living with some random person that pebs met on online
Think about it Chad. The reason this nigga got a place right now is because of fucking bum bitch pebs
because that's pebs friend right the one that live in georgia that's prebs friend or when
that lives off of what is it king street or whatever king's avenue i believe i believe i believe yeah
but she really not know you know i think i had to move in with pebs friend he has a crib right
now he has somewhere to stay at because of pebs friend
That's sad man. Oh
Juice oh
He's a child. Okay
You got you got your your your your mom and daddy, you know, they they pass away you got some money on you got some money money
I don't get did the gay brother get any of that money bitch, huh cuz you know he's gonna spend that
How about you don't donate the motherfucking site juice to hoe huh for his cats for some cat food
huh
Both donate to that to the mouth donate the site man for his kitties
Since you got an inheritance
That they goes give him that he was really giving KK fucking money like it was nothing God damn
What about site huh?
Tell him site. What about me?
Leave me out leave me out
I wish juices bitch ass would come up and fucking say I'm lying about a single fucking thing
Say
For me to go and kiss another man what he paid for my lips to go kiss another man
Hey, hey was fucking with
He was the only one
Are you giving shorty money and she out here getting dicked down by black is and you still paying for them
Black can tell you that never I never beg for a motherfucking thing
What? I have proof of you bet you know, but you begging me to talk to you after ignoring
you for a fucking week. I made you sick to your stomach. Your heart was so fucking goddamn
broken. Shut the fuck up and sit down. No one in your chair fucking turn to speak. Little
boy. You gotta be a fucking straight up. You gotta be a delusional ass simp to still be
No
I
Told him I told him that no matter what he did
It didn't matter that once blockish came around that that was it it was game over and that man
Took that as a challenge
I swear to you he I did tell him that that was it okay more than once he took
that at a challenge that's not my fault I don't give a fuck what anybody has to
say about it that's crazy I believe it though the way he be acting away he'd be
trying to chase these females on the internet bro no did you see what I just
shared on my live
him with tiny Tina she's got a fucking two-foot fucking dildo and she's showing
juice and he's like yeah I could fill you up the same way like what what it was
disgusting it's disgusting he's not even cute when he tries to fucking flirt or
be sexy it's just disgusting
That's fucked up, man. That's fucked up, man.
Got himself a whole girlfriend in here talking about tiny Tina's fucking butt hole and the fucking bedazzle that she has sticking out of her ass.
How turned on he is by it.
That's what fucking ETC men have fucking really become. It's disgusting.
No, I don't I don't know if I can talk to him
We're supposed to rebrand
Jealous over his ex of Miami. Yo, I ignored him for a fucking week. All right. It was beautiful and you know what?
What do you do, what do you do man? What do you do you ignore dogman? What do you do?
He came he came running back paying for them lips to show me how much he was
Yeah
And you said let me pay for them lips you a simp ass motherfucker now you want to call you a liar
He won't call you lying. Come on, man. Come on juice. It's all right juice man
You you already know one as captain save a whore in this community
So it don't hurt to to find this stuff out like don't be hurt nigga. Yeah
We already knew you was a simp, you know
But we know you was going this low man to be chasing women giving them money because they ain't talk to you for a week
Man, that's that's some low
That's some low shit right there, man. I kind of feel bad for you man. You pathetic nigga
You were pathetic milk dud looking ass motherfucker
You know what I'm saying just saying dope
Yeah, if you get on my nerves, and if you get on my nerves, Christine, and
Yo shit is out there. I definitely will
Hey, I'll be back in a few minutes if you're still up. I gotta go charge my phone real quick
Okay, guys. Thanks for letting me up. You're welcome
Yep
Yeah, man, I think I think juice went went to go cry, you know, he went he went to go run into a wall or some shit
Yeah, me
You hear me
That motherfucker went to run into a wall boy
He went to run into a wall like
Where are you
Did you do it?
Hi guys
Um, not particularly, but
I have I it's a laundry, but they ever have night terrors. No
No, like well, I mean I've had nightmares where I woke you up in like a cold sweat. I woke up screaming before but
At night here's not afraid of the door. You have Jamie. Yeah
They're good, thank you
You're feeling that someone is watching you late and I actually wake up
Are you are you jingle after I wake up? Well this morning out because this morning I woke up and I
Like you know with the bathroom we came out of the bathroom and then like
Looked in the screen out in the morning
Waking up in the morning and then I saw like the chat was scrolling and it's crazy said
Thank you. Well, why do you look like that? Are you okay?
What's going on? Oh shit, so my camera was watching me all night
Yeah
At some point, I think it will get so dangerous for me that the FBI will definitely step in.
I'll be like, oh, they're like, oh, too much of the military is going on over there.
Let's calm these down.
So how are we doing?
Anybody want to come up? Anyone want to talk about anything?
Okay, no, let's see
Here's a whole book I have everything you want to know about magic, but we're free to ask
So we can learn a little bit about something
There's some astrology stuff in here
Let's see
If you read about the fool, the fool card, here's what it looks like right here.
There's the fool.
Okay, so the Hebrew letter is Aleph, or it means ox.
And so it is the fool, and it's the sign of air.
Whose card is that?
This is just, you know, I just have this book, and it has, like, you know,
some kind of different interesting insights into the cards.
And so it's maybe everybody's card, because I think this is also, like,
you know, the summer solstice.
Everybody plays the fool sometimes, yeah.
I think it there's the Italian there's like something like just I heard there's a saying like there's nothing better than being the floor
Everyone's to be everyone's to be the floor. I don't know. It's a you know
Rough maybe we're all fools in a way, right, but it's like you'll see it's not a bad thing. Maybe the fool in reverse
but uh the traditional fool it says
It's actually so and it's also a path on the tree of life
It's a little bit gets more complicated when you put Kabbalah into it
So I won't go too much for it is like a path on the tree of life and it says
It's called up so the fool is there and so the path 11 deals with nothing and therefore
We'll have the
Longest description of all paths the card deals with the simple concepts that it takes many words to describe
The most salient feature of the path is that the concept of zero and magic zero is a big
deal.
Zero symbolizes the nothingness of pure being.
This is the zero of the silent minds where quiet divinity is revealed.
The shape of a zero symbolizes the egg, which is a symbol of spirit and magic.
The egg is the unmanifested spirit, pure potential.
The card therefore symbolizes the silence of the yogi.
This is the silence of pure being, the only place where the ultimate essence of life can
be felt.
The fool is the divine fool, drunk and mad on God's essence.
He is also a fool because he moves to the beat of his own drummer and does not follow
the common sense of the common man.
Salvation whatever salvation means is not meant to be obtained on any reasonable terms
Reason is an impulse. Yeah, no reason is an impasse
Reason is an impasse reason is damnation only madness divine madness
Offers an issue Mohammed Napoleon Karl Marx. There's only one thing in common among such persons
They are all mad that is inspired the contradiction of folly
Being equated with wisdom is not uncommon in magical symbolism as obtuse as it sounds most magical truths
Are a seeming contradiction to the rational mind?
It's just one of those things that takes me used to the fool is unlike other cars
Not only the major arcana, but the entire deca 78 cars. Why it is the fool that travels the past
Is he who experiences the rest of the cars?
He is the immaculate soul and the rest of the cars are
Parable regarding his descent into the world of matter and his ultimate return to divinity
Like many of the Hebrew letters, it is not immediately clear what ox has to do with this path.
Frankly, the Hebrew letter attribution can be a little confusing.
These are best left to the student to study through meditation.
I will sometimes give my suggestions as to how Hebrew letter ties everything together.
My interpretations may not be considered nor written as stone.
With regards with through an ox pertaining to this path. Remember that at an oxen can pull opposite and almost unmovable loads
They are more sure-footed than horses and do not jerk the load
Therefore they can pull harder and longer than the horses
This seems to me a hint that our soul is the ox. It is the tireless
is slow-marched on the tree of life into manifestation. We, each of us, are the
fool, busy with wanderlust, just as we know that the dumb ox on the long
journey through the tree of life. Interpreting a path's position between
two Sephiroth also requires a fair amount of finesse. Once again,
interpretation is very depending on the student and circumstances.
It says, I will give clues for my own experiences and interpretations.
For example, on the Tree of Life, this path connects pure divinity, Keether, to wisdom,
Hakma.
To me, this means wisdom comes from being able to find pure joy in every moment.
The fool is happy in any and all circumstances, because for him, there is no final goal.
Each moment of the journey is the meaning, the very reason for his existence.
As the final note, in most historical decks, the Fool went unnumbered, considered to be
distinct from the rest of the deck entirely.
In 1870 America, the Joker appeared in a standard 52 card playing deck.
Similar to the Fool, he's quite similar, or he's quite unlike the rest of the deck.
He's the wild card.
And it says, ritual and meditational use.
You can use that for ritual and meditational use.
It says, for escaping at all, for works of drunken ecstasy,
help with quieting the mind during meditation,
useful for combating fear, weakness, stagnation,
and depression.
Okay, so that's that, but I have more, okay.
So the fool is also, we talk about the divine ecstasy.
I don't think I mentioned Dionysus, okay?
Dionysus is a very interesting God.
Have a book again, and it talks about Dionysus as big the soul that goes down all the passes
But I'll second
Sorry
Okay, so this is about all this will be about the fool in relation to
More inch is more interesting. Yes, they're gonna be a test after this, but it's a very important like if it is interest
You'll like it. I like it. This is a good book
So, okay, so it says the fool
There's as we okay
Since the key to the terror rest in the car is known as the fool during the Middle Ages. He was known as Lord of misrule
But now but now others more
Combalistically inclined call him the babe in the abyss many people simply called him the Joker. This is
This is what he ended up in modern playing card decks
In the early tarot decks, you will find him sometimes dressed in penitential white and sometimes in rags.
Often, he wears feathers stuck in his hair, such as in the bimbo deck, or sports a horned or ass-eared jester's cap.
These are all that are left of his original horns and ass's ears.
The phosphorus, Oster, light-bearing star, as the Greek playwright Aristophanes calls
him, was the youngest son of the Olympian skyfather Zeus, some legends alternatively
named Hades as his father.
In fact, Hades was simply a dark version of the mighty thunderer himself, often being
referred to as Zeus Catechotonicus, or the subterranean Zeus.
Each father diagnosis upon his own sister Demeter
At his birth, he was found to bear small horns in his forehead, like a kid or small cat.
According to the legend that attributed fatherhood to Zeus, Hera, the all-father's ever-jealous
celestial wife, sets a band of monstrous titans to tear the horned child into pieces.
They dismembered him into seven portions, which they boiled in a cauldron and consumed
From it, he prepared a potion, which he administered to the even Princess Senali,
some say the goddess Persephone, causing her to re-conceive the young child. Benishville
Hera, however, ever vigilant, disguised herself as a nurse and persuaded the unlucky Semali
to demand that her divine love reveal himself in all his terrible splendor. In vain,
Zeus tried to dissuade her, but she persisted in her wish to her own destruction.
as indeed the Amnesty and All-Father knew would be the case.
Semi-perished, scorched like a moth in a candle flame at the site of Zeus's terrible radiance.
Hera's vengeance seemed complete, but not quite.
Before Semi fell into the underworld, the All-Father plucked the yet unborn child from her womb
and sealed it in his own thigh until it was due to be delivered.
At that time upon Mount Nisha, he delivered the precious baby into the hands of the God
Hermes for instruction and safekeeping.
The horns, which with Dionysus was born, indicated length with the young horned animal that was considered a suitable sacrificial offering to the gods in the ancient Mediterranean world.
However, not only was he victim of a hunt, but also a hunter in his own right, as his name Zagreus, the great hunter, implies.
In fact, this is his divine father's name also.
So was Dionysus, the younger version of his father, Zeus Karakorotonikos.
The horned child is Bacchus who says he was bestowed the gift of wine upon mankind,
one of the ancient doorways to ecstasy that was serious standing outside one's self.
That is the goal of the magical adventure.
Like his successor Jesus, Dionysus was also an over-turner of high-bound traditions and restrictive tyranny.
He was the incarnate power of spiritual revolt and rebirth.
His traditions path is a medieval European life despite all the efforts made by the church to stamp them out.
And he became known as the Lord of Misrule.
the winter festivities of Christmas and Holy Innocence Day were shadows of his old feast days
held at Saturnalia. During that time of the pagan's amalgamation, Dionysus had been equated with Mithra
on the one hand and the sun on the other. How's everyone doing? Sorry, I'm just reading.
And his birthday was celebrated at the Winter Solstice.
This is the occasion when the sun rounds its nadir and returns reborn from the darkness of the underworld.
Jesus' birth had originally been placed as January 5th by the early Christians.
But as a suggestion, as the more missionary minded, it was backdated to December 25th to coincide with the pagan birthday of the sun.
As late as 1645, a pious Frenchman, Mathurine de Nuer, wrote a letter to Father Pierre Gassendie,
a skeptical mathematician and philosopher, famous for his refutation of Aristotle,
complaining of the ecclesiastical buffoonery at the monastery of Accordier in Antibou in Holy
had been elected obscene song-sang, black masses celebrated at the altars in cakes and sausage
instead of the consecrated hosts, and games played instead of the solemn ceremonials.
The Lord of Mistral also showed his presence at the winter feast of the ass,
and a representation of Madonna and child was led into cathedral sanctuaries seated on an ass.
and they burst left listening to me with sung with hi-haz being chanted by the congregation
and responses. And strangely enough, these practices were officially acceded to by the
church well into the Middle Ages. There was a time and place for everything, even anarchy.
Early Christianity taking over from its pagan forebears was compelled to go along with this
if it wished to maintain a grip on its converse.
All that is left of the Fool's festivities is our modern calendar, Christmas and April
1st.
Boy bishops and burlesque masters aside, the Fool himself played a much larger part in
medieval life than merely to ape at class-steal ceremonies prior to Lent.
In fact, he was often an integral part of every feudal court, attaining considerable
fame in later times.
There, he held an honored position, and his job, apart from merely keeping his master
entertained, was to remind him that, like Caesar, he too was only human and open to air.
Theoretically, the poor fool was the one person at court, immune from retribution to
for quips at his master's expense.
However, all too often, he became the butt for cruel jokes, for like Dionysus, he was
also a scapegoat.
The fool is often portrayed as ragged and unkempt, spurting the waves of the world.
The Mantega Tarot of 1484 shows him simply as a beggar, who, like the Indian Sinyasi,
has nowhere to lay his head, nothing and no one to call his own.
In later decks, he appears and completes Jester's Panopoli with cap and balls and bladder.
He is equated by Rosicrucian Cavalos with Aleph, the first letter of the Hebrew alphabet,
meaning the beginning of all.
However, Florentine Vinciate Dex placed him at the end of the Trump series after the world.
Alpha and Omega were perhaps more accurate.
These practical occultists would also use the image of the fool as a magical nota in
the following manner.
Okay, you like this? Okay. You also like the tarot card. I
Guess there's a couple more pages
We're down kind of shows a little magical ritual
I'll just read one more page looks kind of interesting says according to old legends Dionysus was the reborn younger image of his father
In one branch of the myth, as we have seen, held to be the substrating god of death, Hades himself.
Now one of Hades' chief attributes was the power of invisibility.
He owned a helmet made by Hephaestus, which conferred the power upon him,
and many of the representations of him in Greek art portray him thus, with head turned backward.
Hence the title Hades, which itself means the invisible making.
his son Dionysus also became this characteristic. According to Neoplatonus, the Egyptian version
of the divine child Harpocrates, who was portrayed in ancient art as an infant seated upon a lotus
with a thumb and forefinger into lifts, symbolized both the secrecy and combat upon initiates into
the mysteries and the magical power withdrawal and concealment, according to the time of need.
during the period of pagan amalgamation that a vine child of the pantheon was often linked with
that of another, thus is hardly surprising that the invisible Dionysus born on the understanding
of December 25th came in modern occultist minds with the child's hypocrisy, with
Therefore, when the Acovalus wishes to invoke the power of protection and invisibility,
he meditates upon the image of the tarot fool, often imagining himself in the form of the
figure portrayed on the deck of tarot.
Often, this assumption of God form is combined with a ritual, whether there is any occult
virtue in the actual objects used to these spells, or whether it's simply a game which
sets the deep mind in motion is a masturbated point of monocultist.
And so then you can look into more of just meditating on a tarot card.
And calling up that form in the sticky and they also do similar things to bed and boo boo to them
It's about assuming these God forms
No, I know it was kind of was little okay cast after okay the devil's terror. Yeah
Bible says tests of spirits. Yes
That's car is your favorite you can read about that, too
If you like the you like the tower didn't collect the tower and death Wow guys
Well, you like them in general or do you like?
Yeah, but really it's like even if you get even the scariest hair reading is not it doesn't mean it doesn't mean to you know
You know much about Buddhism? Well, it's an interesting study. I actually I
studied a lot on my own and then
actually
went and
And got initiated into into Mahayana, which is big
Sorry Vajrayana the highest type of but the highest level in Tibetan Buddhism
It's like we're the Dalai Lama. They're all over the world.
Why is everyone in all caps? I don't know. It's yelling.
Do I dream? Yeah, I dream.
Well, I went to Thailand. They have these gigantic giant Buddhas. They're beautiful
Yep
Yeah, the fat Buddha is like actually like a different kind of Buddha. Hey, Jan, how are you?
So we're doing, oh, no one seems to want to hang out with me anymore.
Well, I'll see you guys later.